(Amy:)It's just so much easier
to give him what he wants.
(Leonard:)Oh, true, but think of how
much you've accomplished.
(Leonard:)Who got him to stop
Purelling his pocket change?
(Scene:)Me.
(Leonard:)And who got him to put
things other than gloves
(Leonard:)in the glove compartment?
(Scene:)Me.
(Amy:)It was mittens.
(Penny:)Mm.
(Leonard:)And who got him to
try a turkey dog?
(Amy:)That was actually Koothrappali,
(Amy:)but I did let him spit it out
in my hand.
Look, how can you stop now?
(Leonard:)That's like walking
out of Pinocchio
(Leonard:)right before he
becomes a real boy.
(Amy:)You know, you're right.
(Amy:)I'm in this relationship, too.
(Amy:)I need to stand up for myself.
(Leonard:)Of course you do.
(Amy:)And if he doesn't like it,
he can move back here.
(Leonard:)Oh. He can try. He'd just
need a good locksmith.
(Penny:)Well, who you
gonna hit on?
(Penny:)The girl in front of
us got strawberry.
That's your favorite.
(Sheldon:)No. No, if we both like it,
I'll spend the rest of my life